afternoon children I am Leroy the leftist and I am here to teach y'all fascists are not your
friends they are not let me put on my gloves since we got to handle something real right now
we need to point out the individuals that are currently in a power position that are actively
performing as fascists so that we can identify and name them so that we can shift them now this
lipless lovely Carolyn Leavitt is one of the most confident dummies I have ever witnessed now she is
the White House press secretary remember the definition of a fascist includes characterized
by a dictatorial leader forcible suppression of opposition subordination of individual interest
for the perceived good of the nation or race let leftist Leroy be the first to tell you she is
fascist and you need to know their names and you need to pay attention to what they doing if you
want to make sure that you do everything you can to stop it
fascists are not your friends fascists are not your friends fascists are not your friends so you
should name them name them